♪ In the not-too-distant
Future ♪
♪ Next Sunday AD ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different
From you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
In a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
Cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his boss didn't like him
So he shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send him
Cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find
La-la-la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind
La-la-la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
Begin or end ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call
Cambot! ♪
- ♪ Pan left ♪
- ♪ Gypsy! ♪
- ♪ Hi girl! ♪
- ♪ Tom Servo! ♪
- ♪ What a cool guy ♪
- ♪ Croooow! ♪
♪ Wisecracker ♪
♪ If you're wondering
How he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts
La-la-la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself
"It's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000!" ♪
- One, two, three.
Okay, let's see
what we've got here.
Tom's got paper again.
Scissors cuts paper, I win.
- Ow, ow, ow.
- Okay, Crow, it's our turn,
okay, come on, come on.
One, two, three.
Okay, as you can see here,
Crow's got scissors.
Rock crushes scissors,
and aghh!
- Agh, ow, ow.
- Okay, let's do it again.
Oh, hi, everybody.
Welcome to the Satellite
of Love and Joel
and the Bots here,
and I was just teaching the boys
about a game we used to
play on earth
when I was a kid
called "Rock, Paper, Scissors."
Okay, let's do it again, okay.
One, two--
VOICE ON PA:
Movie's on in 15 seconds.
Joel, I hope you're not playing
too rough with those two.
- No, ma'am.
Okay, here we go.
Agh! Agh! There.
- What was that for?
- Yeah, Joel, play fair.
- Did you just call
"do over," Crow?
- What?
- Crow calls "do-over."
Okay, let's do over,
the three of us this time,
okay, one, two--
- Wait to go, Crow,
my arm's getting numb.
- Okay, let's see.
Hm, looks like
he's got paper again.
- I'm always paper, Joel.
- Rock cuts paper.
Okay and, oh,
this is kind of interesting
'cause look at this, Crow.
It's like you got scissors
and I got scissors this time.
Isn't that something?
- I guess that makes us
even then, huh?
- Well, no, mine are
really sharp scissors.
- Agh! Ow! Ow, ow.
- Commercial sign
three, two, one.
Commercial sign now.
- You guys want to play
mumbly peg now?
- No, no.
- Gypsy crushes Joel.
- We'll be right back.
My babies.
- Gypsy!
- Thank you, Gypsy.
[♪♪♪]
- Oh, my achin' noggin.
- Yeah?
Well, serves you right
for taking advantage of
these little charmkins.
- Oh yeah. Well, you should
ask these little charmkins
what I found oozing out of
my pillowcase this morning.
- Oh, you little baby,
it could have been a lot worse.
- Yeah, at least we killed 'em
before we stuffed 'em in there.
- Enough, you three.
"Freebie and the Bean"
are calling.
- Greetings, homunculus.
Let me set up this week's
invention exchange.
- Let me guess.
They're Good Luck
Troll costumes.
- These Good Luck Troll--
hey, you wrecked my reveal.
- Can we just get on
with this, please.
- Shut up, Frank, or I'll
let the dog play with you.
- Ahh!
- Face it, boobikins,
the Good Luck Troll doll
is a real popular item,
and we want to be popular.
Therefore,
deductive reasoning
demands these adorable
troll costumes.
- Whatever happened
to empiricism?
- That's two, Frank.
Imagine the coos
of young college girls
as they place you
in their purse for good luck
or, better yet,
place you on the nightstand
and rub your belly.
- Oh, yeah, I mean,
nothing makes a co-ed melt
more than looking like
a combination of
Michael J. Pollard,
Yahoo Serious and Buddha.
I mean, I can think
of five-- aghhh!
- Frank--
- I'm out of here, yeah.
- Frank, get back here.
Frank!
Make with your invention
exchange wishnik.
- Well, I'm wearing it.
It's for people
who love the game of pool
or pocket billiards,
and want to take it with them
wherever they go.
It's called "Pocket Pool"
and it comes complete
with green felt underwear
and this handy
ball dispenser.
All right, guys.
Let's rack 'em up.
- Hey, I thought this was
gonna be pocket lawn darts?
- No. Now, I don't want you guys
to put any beer glasses on me
or cigarette butts, all right?
- Hey, Baldilocks,
stop talkin' and start chalkin'.
- All right, gentlemen,
the game is 8-ball and I break.
Oh, I got stripes.
- How do you know?
- I just know, all right?
Okay. Now, this one's...
13 off the side,
off two rails
and a kiss off the 6.
Oh, I scratched.
- That means I'm up, right?
- Hey, you got
a snooker down there.
- Hey, get out of there, you.
- I'm gonna have to use
the bridge for this.
- Oh, let me--
wait a minute, nothing doing.
What do you think, sirs?
- I think you need to work
on your English, Willie Mosconi.
Now, your experiment today
is called "Beatniks."
- Beatniks?
Great, I love that stuff.
- You have no clue
what you're about to endure.
- Beatniks?
Man, I love those guys.
Man, I'm gonna
grow out my troll patch
and rail against
the establishment, man.
[Laughing]
I have seen the best guys
of my emanation
deployed by badness.
Coo, coo.
Agghh!
Agh, agh, aghhh, aghhhhh!
- Into the theater,
Pearl and Getti.
Frank, baby.
[Alarm buzzing]
[♪♪♪]
- Come on.
- [indistinct]
I can't see anything.
- Congratulations, you're
one second into the film.
- Oh, no,
the plaster's coming off.
- Here's your stupid cake.
- Oh, what a lovely cake,
Jessie.
- Thank you. I'm afraid
it's store bought,
but the sentiment
is mine and Bill's.
- Sentiments?
- Yes, it's settled to
the bottom of the cake.
- "Congratulations."
Oh, how nice.
- Yeah.
Who's gonna light that candle?
What did you do, Jessie,
put it on with a hypodermic?
- Ha, ha, well, what else?
- Shut up, shut up, shut up!
- That's beautiful.
- Oh, how nice.
- Now, since it's your
engagement and your cake,
I think you ought to cut it.
- All right, Jessie.
- Blow the candle out.
- I completely
forgot the knife.
- Why the one candle?
- Well, to tell you the truth,
I've never given
an engagement party before
and I don't know
whether it's appropriate.
- To stab you.
- Anyway, I thought
it was kind of pretty.
One candle, first engagement
for Ken and for Cynthia.
- And a first and last
engagement for us both.
Right, honey?
- Right, Ken.
- Maybe.
- Shall I blow out the candle?
- Why not?
- And we all wish you
good things.
We wish you a long life,
many children,
and a happy marriage.
[Sawing noises]
- We shouldn't
say that out loud,
it may not come true.
- What do you mean,
it may not come true?
- Oh, Bill was just quoting,
you know,
superstition, Ken,
that's all.
- Take it back,
take it back!
- I'm very superstitious.
- That explains why you have
garlic in your underwear.
- Oh, thank you.
- Why, Bill never eats
my plaster cake at home.
- Clamp. Sponge.
Suture.
Oh, we've got a bleeder.
There's butter squirting
all over.
Huh. Sponge.
Sponge cake.
- Jessie?
- Thank you.
- Will you, uh, pass
the ketchup please?
- Oh, it looks wonderful,
Jessie.
- There's a layer
of squirrel in here.
- Really, your engagement came
as a kind of surprise.
- Seeing as we're engaged.
- How did it happen?
- Oh, come on, now,
do you want her telling
all the clinical details?
- I don't want
any clinical details.
It must have been
very romantic.
I just thought it would be nice
to hear about it.
- Well, I think
it's an embarrassing question.
- Oh, no, it's not,
Bill, I don't mind.
Well, Jessie, Ken had asked me
to marry him before
so it wasn't really so sudden.
In fact, I'd been thinking
about it for some time.
- She didn't tell me
she was playing hard to get,
if you want to know
the truth, Jessie.
- Shut up, shut up!
- Excuse me.
- I've got to go toss a cake.
- Well, anyway,
one day last week,
Ken dropped by
the [indistinct] school.
- Oh, damn frosting.
Too much flour.
I hate those beamies,
non-pearls,
whatever you call 'em.
Aghh-bleugh!
Pfft.
- Actually,
what really happened,
is I [indistinct]
her over the head
with a building block and...
- Oh, that's his secret.
- He's got
a really nice skull.
- Mm-hm.
- ...say that [indistinct].
- What, at his house?
- I don't know any toast.
Anyway, toasts are to be drunk
at marriages and weddings.
I think we're getting
a little ahead of ourselves.
- All right.
I'll propose a toast.
- Here's to the party
getting better.
- To my bride-to-be.
- Props! Props!
- The most beautiful girl
in the world
from the luckiest guy
in the world.
- And here's to the most
depressing party
I've ever been to.
- Thank you.
- Whoa, really snaked it
in there.
Look at 'em go.
- Oh, oh, Ken.
[Giggling]
- Could someone help me
get the coffee, please?
- Ahhh, why don't you two
just do it on the table?
- You're spoiling
this whole party.
- I'm what?
- Keep your voice down.
- Hey, can we get
some coffee in here?
- We're thirsty in here.
- ...the cake.
- Got any ice cream?
- Setting up
with this knucklehead
doesn't have a chance.
- You are downright insulting.
You could have at least
proposed a toast
when I asked you to.
Look, this party
was your idea.
It wasn't mine.
- Oh, look, for Pete's sake.
[Phone ringing]
- Oh, that's Pete now.
- I'll get it.
[Phone ringing]
- Hello?
- Uh, yes, hello.
This is Peter Props.
Don't eat the cake.
- Yes, he is.
All right, hold on.
- Oh, even the phone's for you,
Mr. Wonderful.
- It's for you, Ken.
- Oh, must be the phone service.
Excuse me.
- Oh, does the great doctor
have a phone service?
- Doctor, phone service
follows you around town?
- Well, how's my patients gonna
get in touch with me
if they have to?
- Yeah. I was kidding.
- Huh, what a dickweed.
- Hello, Dr. Martin here.
- Yes, I'm more important
than him, uh-huh.
- Yes.
- Yes, he is a dickweed.
- Oh, yes.
- Yeah, and rude too.
- Yes, I understand.
Well, how long ago
did she call?
Hm, I see.
- Mm-hm.
- Well, yes, I'll get over there
right away, of course.
- When's our tee-time?
- Thank you.
- Well, I'm gonna go over
to the morgue and cheer up.
- Trouble, Ken?
- Yes, one of Dr. Doyle's
old patients, Mr. Harvey.
- Oh, she's a big rabbit,
you see, there.
- You know, Dr. Doyle hasn't
been feeling too well lately.
He's been in bed for a couple
of days with a virus fever
so I'm elected to go see
Mr. Harvey.
- Oh, I see.
- So I won't be able
to drop you off at home
on the way either, honey.
- Oh, great. Nobody's
gonna help me clean up.
- And I've got to
get there in a hurry.
- Oh, well, that's all right,
I'll take a cab from here.
- I'll get your coat, Ken.
- Don't touch me.
- I don't know
how long I'll be.
I'll come back for you.
- Well, Ken,
why don't you call us
when you find out
more about it?
- We may not want you back.
- Yeah, all right, sure.
Okay, honey.
- Thanks for the laughs.
Sorry I'm gonna miss out
on the Russian roulette.
Ha, ha.
- Well, there goes
the life of the party. Huh.
- Sorry to cut out on you
like this, Jessie.
It was a swell party
while it lasted.
- We all understand, Ken.
- See you, honey.
- Goodbye, Ken.
- So long.
- Another alcohol-free party
ends in shame.
This little playlet
has been brought to you
by the Booze Council,
reminding you to always
stock up on alcoholic beverages
for all your social occasions
because booze really satisfies.
- Booze takes a dull party
and makes it better.
- Booze makes you popular
and heals all wounds.
[♪♪♪]
♪ B-DoubleO-Z-E booze ♪
[Hiccupping]
[♪♪♪]
- Hey, it's Daddio.
♪ E-0-eleven ♪
- Dad, are we there yet?
♪ It's [indistinct]
On my windshield ♪
♪ And tears from heaven ♪
♪ I'm pulling into town
On the interstate ♪
♪ I got a steel train
In the rain ♪
- Edward!
[♪♪♪]
- Dad, I have to go
to the bathroom.
- Go ahead and hurry, please.
- Many thanks for the milk,
wine, beer and ice cream.
- Put your masks on.
- Oh, no, they're gonna do
Kabuki theater.
- Let's go.
- All right, let's stop.
- Let's do some crimes.
- We were expecting you.
- Put your hands down.
- You've got underarm odor,
but you're being held up.
Whaddya do?
- All right, Pop, where
did you hide the rest of it?
- Same place like last time.
- That's good.
- Ah, where's
the fishing lures?
I want a new
Ray Stevens tape.
Where's the jerky?
- Not the ashes.
That's my uncle.
- Don't you boys
ever rob anyone else?
- Sure, but we like you.
- I thought he liked me.
- How much do we owe you, Pop?
- Be my guest.
- Ah, what do you think
we are, moochers?
- Come on, Moon,
handle it and let's go.
- They robbed Paul Wellstone.
- Oh.
- Thanks.
- That's the government
for you.
- And stay away
from that phone, Pop.
Or we'll give you trouble.
- You want the double bag?
- Oops, wrong car.
- Hey, did you get me a Zagnut?
[Horn blaring]
[♪♪♪]
- Glenville, made for
fine-quality youth films.
- The Boatniks, okay.
- Rachel Flynn.
- Travis Bickle?
- Sometimes I wish
the rain would come down
and wash away
all the scum of the city.
[♪♪♪]
- Oh, is the great
Martha Wentworth
going to be in this film?
- Oh, is the great Crow
going to do that joke
every movie?
- Aghhh!
[All imitating theme music]
- I know Grandma lives
around here somewhere.
- Dad, Billy keeps hitting me.
- All right, you two,
cut it out
or I'll turn this thing
right around.
- Well, Grandma
lives on this street.
I recognize it.
- Look, could we just pull over
and ask for directions?
- I know where I'm going.
- Daddy, Billy's
pulling my arm.
- Ah, the family car
trip sketch,
ladies and gentlemen.
[Laughing]
- Well, you just can't
leave it there--
- I'm tripping.
- Don't you know it's against
the law to obstruct traffic?
- What will I do?
It just [indistinct] out.
- Hey, get in.
We'll push you out of the way.
- Okay, but take it easy.
- Sandra Bernhard.
- Oh, thanks a lot.
Can I give you
something for that?
- Hey, what's the matter
with you punks?
- We're beatniks.
- Oh, Iris,
look what you've done.
[Laughing]
- What's the matter
with you kids?
You want to ruin the car?
- Take it easy, eh?
We didn't mean to bend
that pretty iron of yours
but Iris has just
learned how to drive.
Isn't that right, Iris?
- That's very funny,
yes, very funny.
- [indistinct] I don't
understand [indistinct] sumo.
- Come on, [indistinct] move.
[Laughing]
- Oh, Iris, where was you?
I thought you
was gonna help out.
- Does that make you mean?
Does it make you mean mad?
- I'm sorry.
I was busy.
- Yeah, we was out shopping.
- For danger.
- Shopping.
Shopping with what?
The whole bunch of you
ain't never seen
a quarter in one piece.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- What do you call that?
- Gee, Moonie,
I didn't mean nothing.
- Moonshadow.
Moonshadow.
- Did you hear what I said?
Did you hear what I said?
- Drink your bottle of A1
and shut up.
- Want to be a big wheel?
- No, I don't
want to be a leader.
Leaders got too many things
on their minds, man.
I've just got time
for one thing, Eddie, one thing.
[Laughing]
- I don't get you.
It must be some obscure
conceptual thing.
- How much do you think
we got, Eddie?
- Hey, let's see,
three Twinkies,
some [indistinct] ,
a Mars bar.
- Not bad.
That's about $100 apiece,
split four ways.
- Five ways, punk.
- That's right, Iris.
I meant five.
- What'll you have?
Chicken-fried steak's good.
- Can I use your phone?
- Well, the chicken-fried phone
is good too.
- Come on, Nadine, let's get
a little service over here.
You've got
a bunch of live ones.
- That lady's got
an ice bag on her head.
- Live ones, live ones.
Bunch of wise ones.
- Hear that, Chuck?
Little lady's a gas.
- Yeah, a real gas.
- I don't know, it could be
a loose battery connection
but I'm not sure.
- I think
it's my lips are saggy
and my nose is elongated.
- Wait a minute, it's in front
of Nadine's Diner on the--
hey, what street is this?
- 4th Street.
- Thank you.
- It's on 4th Street.
- On 4th Street.
Now, how soon--
oh, you can get over right away?
Well, thank you very much.
- Oh, got to call Cliff Shore.
- Fellas, tell me,
where d'you get the--
oh, where d'you get
all that money?
- She's one of
the Snoop Sisters.
- Aw, come on, Iris,
tell your old mama,
where d'you get the money from?
- Bought short and sold long.
- Mama!
Dry up, and you go out there
and get us some chow to eat.
- Ah, sure I will.
How would you all like some
nice chicken-fried steaks, huh?
- Or is it just
the Margot '56?
- Operator,
this is Harry Bayliss.
I want to place a call
to Harry Bayliss Agency
in Los Angeles.
- That's fine, sir,
but you won't be in.
- Iris, leave it alone.
You'll get it later.
- Oh, Eddie, I was just
looking for some change
for the jukebox.
Ah, come on.
- Okay, okay.
- Just one fun-sized
Snicketts.
- Go have yourself a ball.
- But don't play
Maureen McGovern.
- Operator, I haven't got
any more coins.
Now look,
just reverse the charge.
It's my own office.
OPERATOR: Okay.
- Yes, thank you.
- Come on, Eddie,
let's rock.
- Eww.
- Oh, come on, baby,
just one dance?
- These kids look like
they like to have a lot of fun.
- Just one.
- Hey, it's got to be
a Strauss waltz, okay?
- Dish of ice cream,
don't tempt me.
- Sing to me, baby.
- Get off my back, will you?
- Hey, that's a punch line
for a dirty joke.
- Come on, Eddie.
- Okay.
[♪♪♪]
- ♪ Raw candy baby
You're mine ooh! ♪
- ♪ Leather coat ♪
- ♪ Dish of ice cream ♪
- ♪ Duckbill hair ♪
- Hey, keep it down,
I'm eating a bagel over here.
- ♪ Call me wild ♪
- Oscar Wilde.
- ♪ I don't care ♪
- Yeah, Helen, I got the quartet
all set [indistinct].
- Oh, and I think
I got gigantism.
- Helen, I can't hear
on account of this jukebox.
[♪♪♪]
- ♪ Playin' it cool ♪
- Playin' it cool.
- ♪ Real slick ♪
♪ Havin' a ball ♪
- What's he playing at?
♪ With a crazy chick ♪
- Who, Frances Farmer?
- ♪ Sideburns don't need
Your sympathy ♪
- ♪ Sha-boopy sha-boopy
Sha-boopy ♪
- ♪ "Slow down"
They tell me ♪
- In fact, they tell me
to shut up.
- ♪ How long can it last? ♪
- Eugh!
- ♪ But how can I slow down? ♪
♪ Hey I'm moving too fast ♪
- Oooh!
- ♪ Save your tears ♪
- Would you like to
make a call?
Who was that singing?
- ♪ Don't cry for me ♪
- Argentina!
- ♪ I'll get along ♪
♪ Just let me be ♪
- I'm resolved.
I will kill them.
- ♪ Sideburns don't need
Your sympathy ♪
- Ah, opposable thumb,
I'm impressed.
- You know,
he sold more records
than Elvis or the Beatles.
- Oh yeah.
- Mm-hm.
- ♪ Your sympathy ♪
[Sighing]
- Wow, Joel,
these are some beatniks.
- Whoa, doggy.
Really, really, beatniks.
- I mean, you want
to see beatniks?
This is the movie
that has beatniks in it.
- Yup, ooh, boy.
[Whistling]
Who are we trying to kid?
These people
are no more beatniks--
they're not even boatniks.
Beatnik guys don't wear
sensible shoes, windbreakers
and beatnik women don't wear
campfire girl knicker kits.
If these people are beatniks--
- If these people are beatniks,
then Pat Boone is a beatnik,
Cardinal Stritch
is a beatnik.
- Yeah, yeah, if these people
are beatniks,
then my mom's a beatnik
and she's not.
- "Carousel" had more beatniks
than this movie.
I mean, come on, a real beatnik
would blast across Route 66
with a bottle of George Dickel
and a back seat littered with
empty cans of Iron City beer.
I was hoping to see
week-long heroin jags
and Jackson poker vans
with bullets back--
- I think
they get the point, Tom.
I think
that it'd be a good time
to take this opportunity
to teach the people at home
and in transit
some of the tell-tale signs
that you're probably
not a beatnik, okay?
- Oh, good idea 'cause
either you are or you aren't.
And these people aren't.
- Beatniks.
- Right, right.
- Right.
For example, if you own
more than two polo shirts--
- You're not a beatnik.
- Right. If you own even
one Night Ranger album--
- You're not a beatnik.
- If you find yourself
saying things like,
"I'll be right over
after I clean up--"
- Or, "Hey, come on, I really
like the gym teacher--"
- Or, "Could you please pass
the spring rolls--?"
- You're probably not a beatnik.
- Or if you own
a monthly bus pass--
- Unless it's a pass
to Ken Kesey's bus--
- You're not a beatnik.
- Capiche?
- Done.
- Feels good.
ALL: Beatniks.
[♪♪♪]
- Oh, that was great.
- Eddie, come on,
sing one more.
- After [indistinct]
go ahead, sit down.
- Yeah, get the message.
- Hey, look, get in touch
with Morrisey and--
- Tell him to stop crying.
- Find if he's filled
that spot on his TV show.
- I'll sing you a Moon tune.
- Uh, you need
some time alone?
- ♪ It can happen baby ♪
- Moonie?
- ♪ When you [indistinct] ♪
- You stink.
- You smell like
chicken-fried punk.
- ♪ Well swing [indistinct] ♪
- I think I found somebody.
- He grinds his hips
under the breakfast table.
- Look, I'll tell you
all about it when I get in.
Bye.
- Boy, this is sure a problem .
- Aw, now, Pop,
you asked us to push you.
Besides, we just scratched
the paint a little bit.
- Oh, the car?
Oh, forget about that.
Say, where did you learn
how to sing like that?
- Sing Sing.
- Me?
- No, not you.
I mean, him.
- Call that singing?
That was nothing.
- I was belching.
- Eddie learned his self
to sing, didn't you, Eddie?
- Shut up, Iris.
What are you selling?
- No, I'm not selling.
I'm buying.
You see, I'm an artist
representative.
- I represent Jackson Pollock,
Jasper Johns.
- I'm an agent.
I handle singers and performers
for television.
- Can I have 10%
of your sandwich?
- You want Eddie
to sing on the TV?
- Well, if he'd like to,
I think it could be arranged
but I'd like a couple of people
to hear him first.
- We ain't interested.
Right, Eddie?
- Hey, I ain't no singer.
- I think you are.
- You heard him, Pop.
He ain't interested.
Now beat it.
- Cool it, Moon.
He ain't talking to you.
Look, Mister, he gets paid
and everything, don't he?
- Why, of course.
- How much?
- Well--
- Oh, "Tonight" will pay
$7.50 an hour.
- How much?
- Well, I'd say,
to start about $100.
- A hundred bucks
for [indistinct] big star!
Man, we make that
in one little haul.
- Give me that.
- Well, that's only for one--
- That's peanuts, Mister.
- Well, maybe
it's peanuts to you
but that's only
for one little show.
If you've got what I think
you have, you may be--
- Scabies?
- Who knows, $10,000,
$15,000 a week.
- $15,000 a week?
- Why not?
- Yeah.
- Gosh, I'm stupid.
- Why not?
- Say, anybody here
called for a mechanic?
- Hey, wait a minute,
you said that great.
I'd like to sign you up.
- Now, here's my card, son.
If you get in town tomorrow,
drop in and see me
and we'll see what we can do.
- It's a credit card.
Buy yourself some furniture.
- I don't know.
- Well, just take your time,
son, and think it over and--
but let me know by tomorrow.
- 'Cause I might die.
- And thanks for the push.
- I think
he was being sarcastic.
- Gee, you're gonna see him,
aren't you?
- I don't know.
- Eddie, you become
a big fat star,
you ain't never gonna
forget your buddies
who always stuck by you,
now, are you, Eddie?
- Nah, of course not.
- Ooh, of course not.
- Meanwhile, at the same time,
at the Gotham City Bank.
- Hi, I'm here
for my prostate exam
and I've brought
some of my friends with me.
- I'm Eddie Crane.
I called before.
- Oh, yes.
Mr. Bayliss is expecting you.
I'll tell him you're here.
- The smelly hoodlyums
are here.
- Eddie Crane is here,
Mr. Bayliss.
- Good. Send him in.
- I'll slip out the back.
- You can go in, Mr. Crane.
- Okay.
- Hey, how about us?
- Well, there are
some people inside.
It might be better
if you waited out here for him.
- How about that, Eddie?
Would it be better?
- Hey.
- Uh-uh.
My friends go where I go.
- Now, where's the bathroom?
- See.
- What's your name?
- Helen.
- Who's your daddy?
- Helen Tracy.
- That's my name too.
- Hi, Helen.
- Hi, Eddie.
- Come on, honey.
[Howling]
- Down boy, down boy.
[Humming]
- This is Mr. Morrisey,
the TV station,
and there's Josh Beam.
Josh is gonna play for you.
Ray, this is the boy
I told you about, Eddie Crane.
- How are you, Eddie?
- Okay.
- Looks like this scene
was shot by a bank camera.
- These are my friends,
Iris, Chuck, Red, Moonie.
- I can sing, man.
- Hey, Moon.
- ♪ Baby baby ♪
- Oh, he's the satch
of the group.
- ...put Eddie on the TV?
- Well, I don't know, Miss.
We came down to hear him sing.
If he's anything like--
- Oh, come on, Pops.
Eddie can sing rings
around any of 'em.
He can sing better than any--
- Shut up, Iris.
- But I just wanted--
- D'ya hear what I said?
- Oh, and he's nice
to women too.
- Just sing.
Anything you like.
Josh here can play.
- You read music?
- Nope.
- Hey, do you know,
"With a Look"?
Eddie can sing that.
Right, honey?
- I guess so.
What am I doing here?
I ain't no singer.
- Come on, honey,
do it for me, huh?
- Can I do it for her?
- Okay, I'll do it for you.
- This is going out to
one of you, whoever you are.
- Play.
[♪♪♪]
- I am Ironman.
- ♪ With a look
You can make me laugh ♪
[Laughing]
♪ With a look I just melt
And don't know why ♪
- He'll be gone in a minute.
- ♪ All I know is I glow
With a warm sensation ♪
[All mumbling]
♪ Your eyes
Hold a wonderful-- ♪
- Wow, he's singing to me,
for cryin' out loud.
He likes me.
- ♪ A sensation ♪
♪ With a look I fell
Succumbed to your charms ♪
- ♪ When I knock over
A grocery store ♪
♪ All I want
Is to whip a clerk ♪
- ♪ We were in
Each other's arms ♪
- Geez, he's gonna song
the whole song, isn't he?
I mean it.
Oh my God, oh.
- ♪ And what more could I do? ♪
- ♪ You could stop singing ♪
- ♪ I fell hopelessly
In love with you ♪
- Gee, I'm touched.
I didn't know
you felt that way.
- ♪ Oh so hopelessly in love-- ♪
- ♪ With myself ♪
[Applause]
- Fantastic.
Really fantastic.
That was an adagio, wasn't it?
- Gee, that was great, honey.
- Well, Harry, you were right.
- It's a comfortable chair.
- I don't know how
he'll hold up on the show
but, ha,
I'll take a chance.
- Good. Well, the show's
tomorrow night
so we better get you
checked into a hotel.
Take care of that,
will you, Helen?
- All right.
- Wait a minute,
what about my friends?
Where are they gonna stay?
- Well, I didn't know
you were coming into town--
- Hey, what about that?
- Either they stay with me
or I go.
- Now, just a minute, son.
- Don't give me that "son" bit.
Either they stay or I go.
- Pull my finger.
- All right,
all right, Eddie.
Helen, put them all
up in a hotel and--
- Kill them.
- ...get you a new outfit
for the show
and, well, anything else
he may need.
- Right.
- But be sure he gets back
for rehearsal tonight.
See you tomorrow.
- Hate that guy.
Who hates that guy?
- I do.
- I do too.
- Uh-oh.
Smells like a montage.
- All right, you're gonna go
into that [indistinct]
and you're gonna tell
the lady what you took.
- No. No, not if you want
to be taken seriously .
[Laughing]
- What a moron.
- All right.
I like it.
I'll take 300 of these shirts.
- I'm school shopping
with Mom.
- Oh, I-- you know,
I think I need
some drinks for school,
too, Mom.
- ...The food is excellent.
- She's a ventriloquist.
- And she's fantastic.
- Would you like heavy smoking
or moderate smoking?
- Oh, great.
Here comes a big tip.
He'll have the club.
She'll have the cottage cheese
with a peach slice.
- Oh, I'm hungry.
Shopping for men's clothes
is a lot harder than I thought.
- Uh, what's pesto?
- Do you like
the things we picked?
- We?
You mean, you picked.
I wouldn't have known
what to get.
Thanks, Helen.
- For making us laugh
about love again.
- Well, what shall we eat?
Want to start
with a cocktail?
- Yes, ma'am!
- I don't think so.
I feel like
I'm loaded already.
- You're pretty excited,
aren't you?
- I guess so.
I'm in the show tomorrow,
and the clothes
and this place.
I never thought
I'd be doing this.
- What, buying clothes?
- I can't even believe
it's happening to me.
- Well, it is.
And it's you, all right.
And this is
only the beginning.
- Geez, I'm stupid.
I forgot how stupid I was.
- Yeah, but me.
I never done anything
to deserve it.
- Not a high school diploma
between 'em.
- ...stumbled along
taking what I wanted
'cause I knew nobody
would ever give me anything.
- I'm sensitive.
- Getting pushed around so long,
you start pushing back.
Hard in the heart.
You get to like it.
- Thanks for the character
development.
- You feel like somebody.
- What, Eddie?
What do you feel?
- I feel like--like--
- An onion.
- Ah, forget it.
- No, no, please?
Tell me.
- I feel I can't keep
my hands off you.
- Police! Police!
- Why, I don't mean
nothing like that.
I mean, like,
when I first saw you.
I felt I'd been away somewhere
for a long time
and I was coming home
and you were waiting for me.
- I've never seen an
injection-molded face before.
- Your eyes were saying,
"Eddie.
Eddie, where you been?"
Like I'd known you forever.
I wanted to hold you
and tell you I'm never
gonna leave you again.
That's how I felt.
- Well, are you two
ready to order?
- Now have a good laugh.
[Laughing]
- Eddie, I'm not laughing.
- I'm panicking.
- You're not, are you?
Boy, I must be flipping.
I never talk like that
to anyone.
No kiddin'.
- Except my dog.
- I never formed
a complete sentence before.
I forgot who I am.
- You're my sad clown.
[♪♪♪]
- Whoa, stop it.
There's a big sign.
Whoops. Oh.
- Now, ladies and gentlemen,
the Talent Showcase continues
as we present a young man
who's making
his first appearance
as a singer tonight.
We know
you'll enjoy the talents--
- [indistinct] Miller.
- Eddie Crane.
- Well--
- I said, "Let's hear it
for Eddie Crane." Eddie Crane.
Eddie Crane,
ladies and gentlemen.
♪ Oh summer plate ♪
- Aghh!
- ♪ Anything ♪
- ♪ Is better than this crap ♪
- ♪ Desire your slightest
Wish is my command ♪
- He's singing into
a refrigerator.
- ♪ There's nothing I won't do ♪
♪ I'm so in love with you ♪
♪ Anything-- ♪
- Oh, yes, yes.
- ♪ Your little heart desires ♪
- Oh, I desire you
to stop singing.
- ♪ Just say the word
And I'll be on hand ♪
♪ To make your dreams
Come true ♪
- Aghhh!
- ♪ Should want the moon-- ♪
- Hmm, maple syrup.
It's good.
- ♪ And the stars that shine ♪
- Yes, yes.
Oh, yeah, good one.
- Here's a singer
for our generation.
- ♪ Just to prove to you ♪
♪ You're the only one
I'm dreaming of my darling ♪
- Good thing they're shooting
him from the waist up, huh?
- ♪ Your little heart desires ♪
♪ I just can't do enough-- ♪
- Wait a minute, that's the guy
who robbed my store.
- ♪ To make your life complete ♪
- Huh, he went to gesture B.
- ♪ If you should
Want the moon-- ♪
- He should seriously
consider a soul transplant.
- ♪ And the sun from above ♪
- Boy, beatnik music
is really square.
- ♪ I'll tell them
From the blue ♪
♪ Just to prove to you-- ♪
- He kind of reminds me
of a singing weatherman.
- ♪ That you're the only one
I'm dreaming of my darling ♪
♪ Anything-- ♪
- Aghh!
- Oh, he looks
really bad there.
- ♪ Your little heart desires ♪
- Inside Daisy [indistinct]
- ♪ I just can't do enough
My sweet ♪
- This is one from
Ginsberg's ballad years.
[Applause]
- Fantastic.
That is fantastic.
- Next up, Geechy Guy.
- That's it, Eddie.
Nice work.
- Thanks very much.
- What's the matter with you?
We're hot,
we're are on the air.
- Aghhh!
- Death of a stage manager.
- Moon, break it up,
what are you doing?
- Say, what's the trouble here?
- I'm out of beer.
- Nothing, Mr. Bayliss.
It's just a little
misunderstanding.
- Eddie, Mr. Morrissey
would like to see you
at his office
for a moment.
Can you come in--
- Nude?
- Alone?
- Yeah, sure.
You guys wait out here.
I'll be right back.
- Come on.
- Uh, that's the problem
with long necklaces.
- Well, here he is, Ray.
- You want a shot at him?
- Congratulations, Eddie.
You have a lot of talent.
- Thank you, sir.
- Now why don't you kids
go over there and sit down
and let a couple of
old men talk business, huh?
- So how's the hernia?
- As you know, I just have
a local station here
but I do believe
they'd talk contract
and build a show
around your boy,
if you're interested.
- Want some bread?
- ...but you know I don't
want to tie Eddie up here.
Now you understand this.
- Oh-ho.
I can't say I blame you.
- Ooh, I became a switchboard.
- Oh, I'm back again.
- Mr. Morrisey, we're getting
all kinds of calls
about Eddie Crane.
They think he's terrific.
- Well, that's wonderful.
Thank you, Grace.
Hear that, Eddie?
- Looks like you're
on your way.
[Phone ringing]
- They're still calling.
- Yes?
- Yes, Mr. President.
- Who? Put him on.
It's Walter Letterman of
Universal Records about Eddie.
- This is the President.
- Hello?
- Yeah? Put him on.
- Yes, Mr. Letterman.
Yes, he was sensational.
- Yeah.
Now, go to the window.
- Our switchboard's been lit--
what's that?
- Go to the window.
- No, he's not
under contract to me.
- Forget the contract.
What are you wearing?
- Oh, I see.
Well, his agent
is right here.
- Oh, what's he wearing?
- Talk to him, Harry.
- Hello, Mr. Letterman.
This is Harry Bayliss.
- Yeah, just like,
"It's a Wonderful Life,"
Harry Bailey.
Yeah, very funny.
- Snookums.
- Well, that's a little quick,
isn't it?
Oh, yeah, sure.
We could rehearse
all day, yeah.
- But we won't.
I'm too old for that.
- Oh no, don't worry.
We'll be there.
Yeah, thank you very much.
- Boy, he's a tough negotiator.
- Mm-hm.
- Kid, I got you
a $100 lifetime deal.
- Come on, kids,
break it up.
- Huh?
- What do you think, Eddie?
- About what?
- What's the matter, Eddie,
weren't you listening?
- Dah-huh?
- Eddie, looks like
you're an overnight sensation.
- And it hasn't
even been overnight.
- ...recorded all night
for immediate release.
- No kidding. Me?
- Yeah, do you know
what that means?
If you hit--
- I'll need more socks?
- ...top show.
And then
when you're ready for it,
the "Eddie Crane Show."
- Then, "Eddie's World."
- So quick.
- Well, that's the way
it happens in this business.
Sometimes it's fast
or not at all.
- Yeah, I see what you mean.
- But don't kid yourself, son.
- You're not that good.
- It's gonna mean
an awful lot of hard work.
And I hope you're up to it.
- Mr. Bayliss,
all my life,
I've been kicked around
for nothing.
I ain't afraid of working
to get some place.
- Thanks, son.
I know you won't
let anybody down.
- No, sir.
- Mind my hinder.
- How long we supposed to cool
our heels out there, man?
- Moon, do you hear the news?
I'm gonna make records.
- No kiddin'?
- Yeah, ain't I, Mr. Bayliss?
- That's right.
- Yahoo!
- Yeah, that's crazy.
- Hey, this calls
for a celebration.
Come on, let's shake
this town up tonight.
- Now, hold on here,
just a minute.
Now, I know you're all
happy about this
but Eddie's
got to get some rest.
He's recording
tomorrow night, you know?
- What you talkin' about?
My Eddie's a big star now.
He don't have to worry
about singing.
He can do it with his eyes
closed, can't you, honey?
- Yeah, I feel fine.
- Yeah, I think
Mr. Bayliss is right.
There'll be plenty of time
to celebrate later on.
You could catch cold
or something.
- And drive to Houston.
- What are you, his mother?
- I didn't mean--
- Iris! Maybe they're right.
I got to protect my voice.
- Well, pick up a neckerchief.
- Or maybe we just ain't
good enough for you now.
Is that it?
- Shut up all of you!
I ain't walkin' out on nobody.
It's just--
- It's just
that I love pancakes.
- Oh, I don't know.
Come on, let's go back
to the hotel.
I'll see you tomorrow.
- Eddie?
- Yeah?
- Good luck.
- Yeah, thanks.
- Let's go, baby.
- Helen?
- Hayes, Gurley Brown,
Keller, Wheels?
- That sofa's actually
a seat of a pick-up truck.
[♪♪♪]
- When in Hollywood,
be sure not to stay
at the Hollywood Inn.
- Whoa,
she's having an episode.
- Geez, Moon, no.
- It's a huge
transistor radio.
- Send us up some ice.
- Send up some more
fruit soda.
And some chuckles.
- Huh? Yes, water.
Laugh juice.
Don't you know nothing?
Booze!
Yeah, lots of booze.
- Sid and Nancy.
- What do you mean?
Sure, we're old enough.
D'ya want to see
my driver's license?
Why, you--
Aghhh.
- What's up, man?
- Ah, that old dot
downstairs cut us off.
- Ahh, kids.
- Well, I know where we can
get all the lush we want, man.
- Where?
- It's about two hours'
drive from here.
- Oh, Hudson, Wisconsin?
- ...liquor store?
We can't stick him up.
His two weeks
ain't up yet.
[Laughing]
- [indistinct] man,
why don't you join the party?
What's the matter,
are you afraid
you might be
catching a cold, man?
- Maybe he just want to be
with that sweet little nothing
you've been
making eyes with, huh?
- Get off my back, Iris.
I'm thinkin'.
- Dreamin' is more like it.
You're dreaming how
you're gonna be a big fat star
and how well you and Helen
are gonna hit it off.
Isn't that it,
big shot, huh?
- Yeah, I'm big boned, okay?
- That's not right.
- Maybe you'd just
like to walk out on here
and you can forget
you ever knew us.
Isn't that it?
- I told you
to leave me alone.
- Next time, I'll punch you.
- Yeah, I got your message.
- I'm sorry.
I guess I just blew my stack.
[Knocking on door]
- I'll get it.
- The geeknik.
- Domino's.
- Yeah?
- I'm the hotel manager.
What's going on in here?
I've had complaints
from every room in the house.
- What's the matter, egghead?
Can't we have a little fun?
- Oh! Oh, my goodness,
what have you done to the room?
This is terrible.
Hey, you'll pay for this.
- My goodness,
you'll pay for this.
- Is that how I sound, really?
- You--
why, you young hoodlums.
I'll call the police.
- No magic pimpers
for you, young man.
- Say one word to anyone
and I'm gonna moon you.
- You're gonna what?
- Moon you!
- You know,
hang my butt out.
- You can rely on me.
I won't tell a soul.
But who's gonna pay
for the damage here?
- Just put it
on the bill, Mister.
I'll see it's taken care of.
- Thank you, sir.
- Now you get on out of here
before we change our mind.
- You can trust
in my discretion. I--
- Get!
- Sure.
- He's the shakiest
hotel manager in the west.
[Laughing]
- Boy, wasn't he scared?
Well, you can
trust my discretion.
- The next John Byner.
- ...calls the cops.
- He won't.
He's so chicken,
he could grow feathers.
[Laughing]
[♪♪♪]
[Singing]
- Oh, I'm so glad
Joel isn't here.
He'd just be ruining
everything right now.
Hey, are there any more
corn curls, Crow?
Crooooow?
- Crow T. Travis.
No, no.
Mrs. Tony T. Travis.
No?
No, too Italian.
Mr. and Mrs. Tony
and Crow Robot-Travis.
No, that's too long.
Wonder what Tony's
thinking about right now.
- Oh, I don't know.
He's probably
driving round real fast
in his super-cool car
and stuff like that.
Couldn't you just scream?
- Aghhhh!
- Oh, Tom,
you are so childish.
When you become a woman,
you'll understand these things.
The Tony I know
is a very serious man.
Compassionate
and thoughtful to a fault.
He goes to church
every Sunday.
- Wonder what denomination.
- Oh, please, Crow,
where d'you read that?
I just happen
to have the latest on Tony
in this month's "Tigerbot."
"Tony, fun-loving loner."
And it says, "Tony lives
with his parents in Burbank
"and loves to swap jokes
with Jay Osmond,
"the comedian
of the Osmond family.
"Sometimes you can find him
riding round the five acres
"behind his house
on his mini-bike
"or making funny faces
in the mirror
to crack himself up."
Ahh.
- I read in "Dynamite"
that he likes [indistinct].
- Oh, turn around, Gypsy.
Servo, you don't know
nothing about him.
Tony, and I know this
for a fact, girlfriend,
is producing
and starring and writing
and singing the theme song
for a movie about
his whole life story.
And on weekends, he's training
to be a Navy Seal.
- Oh, wow.
- Hey, so, guys, I got
all the rest of your stuff.
I think you're all settled in
for the evening now.
- Yes, Joel.
- You know what,
you guys are really into
this Tony Travis guy,
you know?
You know,
when I was your age,
that's when the teen idols
had faces, you know.
There was David Soul
and the Brady Girls
and Jeremy Gelbwaks
and Tony DeFranco
and the DeFranco Family.
Don't forget Donny Most.
- Spare us.
- You know, Tony Travis.
Now, wait a minute,
now that I think about it,
I think we went to
the same high school together.
- What?
- In fact, I think
I've got his number
right there on speed-dial.
It's marked "Tony T."
You should call him.
He's a real nice guy.
Go on, call him.
- No, no, no.
Oh, I can't do it,
I can't do it.
Hold it.
Should we?
- I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna do it.
Tony T.
- I'm gonna die,
I'm gonna die.
I can't do this.
I need a shower.
Oh, oh, it's ringing,
it's ringing.
- Hello ?
- Oh, Tony.
- This is Tony Travis.
Sorry I'm not in right now.
I got called in to cover
for Roy over at the Taco Hell.
If everything goes right,
the sour cream gun don't jam,
should be home around 9.
If you'd like to leave
a message for me,
Gary, Rick,
Jeff, Rahoul,
Terry, Prairie Don
or any of the kids,
leave it
at the sound of the tone.
Or if you're a bill collector
or you're with the military--
[beeping]
- Oh, sad.
- No, can you believe it?
Oh, it is better
to have loved and lost
than never
to have loved at all.
- Tony.
- You know,
I liked the Moon guy.
- Yeah.
- Moon, yeah,
the Moon, yeah.
- Hey,
it's Charlie's Café beer.
[♪♪♪]
- Hey,
that's a handicapped spot.
- Hey, it says
"Dine and dancing."
You want to go in here?
- Well, let's go somewhere.
I don't want to
drive around all night.
- Especially, 'cause
it's 2 in the afternoon.
- This is probably
the best place in L.A.
- Oh, come on,
they serve drinks.
- Yeah.
- Beatniks rowdy party
of six, please.
- Ba-ba-boom!
- Hey, schooch over.
- Let me in.
- Hey!
- Oh, bad touch.
- Call this meeting to order.
- Hey, hey, take it easy.
Don't you see
there's people eating here?
- Oh, I'm awfully sorry,
Charlie.
We didn't know you were
running a graveyard.
- Yeah, it says,
"Dine and dancing"
so where do we dance, Charlie?
- Right here,
and I ain't Charlie, I'm Gus.
- Well, where's Charlie?
- We want Charlie.
- Whoa, bad touch.
- Well, I never.
- You gonna throw us out,
Charlie?
By yourself?
- All right, all right.
What'll you have?
- How about a menu?
I'm hungry.
- How would you like that done?
- The kitchen's closed.
- Well, get with it, man.
Open it.
- You heard the lady, Charlie.
- Well, maybe I can fix
some ham sandwiches, okay?
- Yeah, all the way around.
- Goodnight, folks.
- Yeah, we'll be back
real soon.
- What to drink?
Coffee?
- How about some booze?
- Sorry, no liquor.
- No liquor and no food.
What are you staying open for,
Charlie?
- The name's Gus,
and no liquor after 2.
- It ain't 2 yet, Charlie.
- Go get the sandwiches.
We're hungry.
- I can't believe
they're manhandling him
for a sandwich.
- They're probably
hypoglycemic.
- ...rock.
- Sure, honey.
- Hey, my first hit
record's out already.
Play me for me.
Heh, heh, heh, heh.
[♪♪♪]
- Felix, where's
the eagle snacks?
- Well-stocked bar.
They got four bottles.
- Mm-hm.
[♪♪♪]
[Music stopped]
- Eddie Crane unplugged.
- He hit Big Jake.
- Hey, I was watching
"She's the Sheriff."
- You want to watch TV,
go home, okay?
No living room.
- Why, you great big
wonderful man.
- Wait, I know,
you're Libra, right?
- Penny for your thoughts.
- He's wearing a sports bra.
[Laughing]
- Pass the fondue!
- Well, he seemed nice.
- Mm-hm.
[♪♪♪]
- Open bar.
- Literally.
- Here, Worcestershire.
- Heinz 57 for me, please.
- Hey, hey,
where d'ya get that?
- My aunt's house.
- What are you, Charlie,
a cop or a bartender?
- You're a pretty smart punk,
aren't you?
You took it off of my bar.
- I don't see your name on it,
Charlie.
- Yeah, my name is
Jack Daniels, all right?
- ...punk, and if you
don't put that bottle
back where you found it from,
I'm gonna give it--
- [indistinct] gratuity.
- Hey, look, Moon, I'm scared.
He's got us surrounded.
[Laughing]
- Okay, that's it.
Go on, get out of here.
All of you, blow.
- Put your lips together
and blow.
- Don't you hear me?
[Blowing]
[Laughing]
- Okay, you asked for it.
- Oh, you asked for it.
I'm overcooking your fries.
- Is that today's liturgy
on the board over there?
- Now just sit there.
You too.
I warned you.
[Dialing phone]
- Hello, give me
the Sheriff's office.
Now you punks'll get it.
- Hey, oh, Charlie.
- Today's temperature is--
- Don't do that, Charlie.
- He's an evil Gilligan.
- Hm, he's going out of his way
to be loathsome.
- Come on, will you?
We were just having
a little fun, Charlie.
- Let me talk to Sergeant--
- Oh, come on, Charlie.
Will you give us a break?
I'll put the bottle back
and we'll pay for what we drank.
- Well, you put it back
and then we'll see.
- Hello, Mike?
Yeah, Gus.
- Please!
[Crying]
- Geez!
- Never mind, Mike.
Listen, I'll call you back.
- Peter Breck,
ladies and gentlemen.
Peter Breck.
- What an eccentric
performance.
- I'll never be [indistinct].
- Ooh! That was our best wine.
- A good year.
- Iris, get the door
and keep a look-out.
- Now we've got to make
our own sandwiches.
- What d'ya have
to hit him for?
- What did you want me to do?
Kiss him, big Ed?
- Ah, you--
- You're the second person
who's called me "You."
- Let's get him outside.
- Is he dead?
- No, just bent a little.
Come on.
[Car tires screeching]
- Someone's coming.
- I think it's love.
- Quick!
You work the fryer.
You hostess.
Hand out those menus.
I think we're here, Michael.
- All right, cover us.
Iris, come with me
and play it cool.
- Yeah.
- Come on, baby.
- Honey.
- Hey, you!
- I'm not "You."
- Get in the car, Iris.
- May I take your order, sir?
- What do you want?
- What's going on inside?
- Must marry ketchup bottles.
- What d'ya mean?
- You know what I mean, fella.
Any action?
Any women,
chicks, broads?
- Oh, no, man.
The joint's dead.
There's nobody there.
They're closing up.
- Hey, you, uh, scored, huh?
- Yeah, got two assists.
- Yeah, I scored.
- Okay, boy.
Take it easy now.
- Hot dog, at least
somebody scored.
I can go home to bed now.
[Gun firing]
- Oh, my ankle, uh, shoulder.
- Order!
- Eddie, I've been hit.
I'm hit.
- [indistinct]
- Just kind of hang.
- I don't care
who hit who first.
Come on.
- Suddenly,
it's the last picture show.
- So I guess
happy hour's over, huh?
- Uh, a re you hiring?
[♪♪♪]
- It's a newborn gun.
- Implication playhouse.
- Come on, Moon, let's go.
What's going on?
- Just cleaning up.
- Come on.
- Oh, that's considerate.
- Come on, Moonie,
get in the car.
We ain't got forever.
- I call the back.
- Please, Eddie,
get some help for me.
[CRYING]
I don't want to die.
- You crybaby punk,
are you afraid to die, man?
[Laughing]
- Shut up!
You got us into--
- Wipeout!
- You went back
and killed that barkeep
for no reason, didn't you?
You went back
and killed him, didn't you?
- Yeah.
- Why?
Why did you have to do it?
Why?
- I done it for you, Eddie.
- For me?
- And I didn't
kill you anybody.
- Why for me?
- I didn't care
none about myself.
When I went back into that bar,
that fat barkeep Charlie,
he says--
- What are you talkin' about?
- He said he was gonna remember
what we all looked like
and spill to the cops.
- You're lying.
- No, I'm not.
- You're exaggerating.
- ...thinking, Eddie,
about you going on television.
And how he might see you
and how he might
recognize you, Eddie.
Send you up for life.
Might even burn you, man.
- Burn me?
Nobody's gonna burn me.
I ain't never killed nobody.
- Sure I wanted to.
- You're in it
just as much as I am.
We're all in it, together.
You know that,
don't you, Eddie?
Don't you, huh?
- You're different.
- Yeah.
Take it easy.
- Sort of a gender-bending
Camille.
- He looks like a big
ventriloquist dummy.
- Does that hurt bad?
- It throbs a little.
- Like my heart
when I look into
the pitiless void of hell,
man, hell.
- How's it look?
- Uh, have you ever had
[indistinct].
- Iris, get me that bottle.
- I'll go boil some towels.
- This might sting, Red.
- Sting Ray.
- The famous Red Button's
death scene.
- That's in case
you want to yell.
- Oh-waghhhh!
- Oww!!
- Give him a beer bath .
- He's out.
- Maybe that's good.
- What do you think, Eddie?
Will he be all right?
- Well,
I'm just a nurse's aide.
- I dunno, but you can thank
Gun-happy over here.
We're in real trouble now.
- Thank you, Gun-happy.
- No witnesses.
I took care of that.
- Did you?
What about the guy
that was sitting at the bar?
He got a real good look
at all of us.
- Oh, rot!
- You're always
ruining my fun.
- Man, he can't prove nothing
he didn't see.
- Oh, I see.
What about Red, here?
How are you gonna
explain the hole in him?
Say a vampire bit him?
- Uh, that won't
hold up in court.
- Helen was right.
How did I ever get mixed up
with a crazy bunch like you?
- We had two [indistinct].
- I must be nuts myself.
- What?
How did you get
mixed up with us?
You hear that, Moonie?
How did you--
Just who do you think
you are, big shot?
- Yeah?
- He's wearing his truss
on the outside.
- He's got his holster on.
He knows he's going
to the big valley.
- Well, it don't wash off,
Big Eddie.
You're one of us.
You've always been one of us
and you are gonna stay
one of us.
Are you hip? Huh?
- Nice to have job security.
- Eddie, she's given you
a lot of crazy ideas.
She's getting you
all mixed up.
She'll never do for you
like I will.
- Eughh!
- Eddie, where you goin'?
- Out.
I got a lot of thinkin' to do.
- Hey, he's following
a makeover in "Glamour."
- Apply cream to--
- Montage.
- There were a million stupid
stories in the naked city
and this is the stupidest one.
♪ Everybody's talkin' of me ♪
- ♪ Stayin' alive
Stayin' alive ♪
♪ Ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Stayin'-- ♪
- ...in here!
- Oh, sorry ma'am.
- Let me see, what was the--?
Oh, yeah.
♪ 867-5309 ♪
- ♪ Hudson 327-hundred ♪
- Hey, now, we can't hear.
[Phone ringing]
- Wait a minute,
she's sleeping in a drawer.
- [GRUFFLY]
Joe's Pool, ahem ,
[FEMALE VOICE]
Joe's Pool Hall.
- Hello? Helen?
Hi, this is Eddie Crane.
- Eddie?
- You know,
I sit behind you in Phy. Ed.
- I just wanted
to speak to you .
- I'm glad you called
but it's so--
- I don't know
why I called you.
- Well, I'm glad you did.
Eddie, is something wrong?
What is it?
- Got kind of a tummy ache.
- Is it the show, is that it?
- I ain't worried about
my career or shows or nothing,
'cause I ain't
gonna do no shows.
- What are you saying?
- I want out,
that's what I'm saying.
I ain't your boy,
you made a mistake.
I can't sing or nothing.
- Why, you have
a wonderful talent.
Please don't
throw it away now.
- I threw it away
a long time ago.
- Eddie, please, if I've done
anything to change you--
Is that it?
- Can't you get it
through your head,
it is nothing
to do with you?
It's me. Me!
I'm no good,
I'm just no good.
- Stop trying to co-depend
all over me, Eddie.
- I got to get away
from you, from me.
- What's wrong?
- Tell Mr. Bayliss,
"Thanks for believing in me."
Now I got to hang up.
- Eddie, are you there?
Eddie, answer me.
- Yeah, I'm here.
- Sorry, my ear
stopped working.
That's better.
- You asked me this afternoon
if I felt what you did.
I love you, Eddie.
- Huh?
- I don't know how or why.
It's all so quick
but I do, I love you.
- Oh, we bought
a shirt together.
Big deal.
- ...crazy and mixed up,
I feel I'm still asleep
but I know what I'm saying.
I love you.
You can't just go away
and disappear like that
with a telephone call.
- I've got no choice.
I've got to get away.
- But why now?
Why right this minute
when your whole life
is opening up for you?
A once-in-a-lifetime
chance of success.
People would give anything for
a chance like you're getting.
- What's in it for you?
- A 10% commission.
- Me?
- Yeah.
You're making a big pitch.
What's in it for your end?
A lot of quick cash, maybe,
if Eddie hits the big time?
Is that it?
- You think I told you
I love you
because I want to keep you here
for business reasons,
to make money off of you?
- What is this,
1-900-TALK-FAST?
- Well, for your information,
there have been hundreds of
new talents I've been around.
Do you think
I told 'em all I loved 'em
just to keep them
signed to a contract?
- [indistinct].
- I never told anyone
anything like that before.
- Does she have coffee filters
on her headboard?
- I never loved anyone
until I met you.
Now I'm sorry I told you.
- Helen, you don't understand.
- I understand it's all over
before it got started.
Thanks for telling me now
before I made
a real fool of myself.
- Helen, wait, please.
- Goodbye.
- Soup pie?
- Helen?
I'm coming over.
- Yeah, go over there,
tell her a thing or two and--
wait a minute,
where does she live?
[♪♪♪]
♪ I been walkin'
These streets so long ♪
♪ I was walkin' in Memphis ♪
- Kolchak: The Night Stalker.
- 8 :45.
I was outside
Frank Gannon's house.
He didn't know
I was there but--
- She lives in a library?
- I'd like to check out
a girl, please.
- [indistinct].
- How did you find me?
- Yeah.
- We just took a number
out of the phone book,
figured you'd show up here.
All set to spill your guts
out to mama upstairs,
all about how the big, bad boys
made you do things
and how you didn't
want to do those things.
- Oh, scientology.
- Number 3 step forward
and turn left.
- You're flipped.
- Why don't you
lay off him, Moon?
Eddie wouldn't do that,
would you, Eddie?
- Hey, he got a line.
- Wow! Cool!
- Of course not.
What do you think I am, Eddie?
- A crappy actor?
- You got him wrong.
Eddie wouldn't run out now,
specially with Red so bad off.
- How is he?
- Gee, not good, Eddie.
He's real hot and moanin'
and talkin' funny.
Hey, what are we gonna do
with him?
- Oh, he's in love.
- What are you asking me for?
- 'Cause you're the leader
of the gang, Eddie.
- ♪ The leader of the gang ♪
- Yeah.
- Come on, let's go.
- And would you straighten
your spine?
- Please.
- Eddie, what are we
gonna do with him?
- I dunno.
- Well, we can't
leave him like that.
He may croak.
[Croaking noises]
- We'll have too many problems.
- Shut up, Moon.
- Got to try to get him
to a hospital right away.
- General Hospital!
- Sure, walk over
to the hospital,
up to the desk and we say,
"We'd like to make a deposit
in the gunshot wound
department."
Oh, that's real smart, Iris.
- Can't we just drive him over
and leave him there?
- And have them ask him
how he got shot?
He'd drag us all into it.
- Red wouldn't talk,
would he, Eddie?
- Moon's got a point.
We can't go out with him
in daylight.
- He has sensitive skin.
- Okay, we'll wait
until tonight.
Then we'll get out of here
and take him to a doc
in a small town somewhere.
- How about a dock in the bay?
- Ta-doom!
- I only hope
he holds out 'til then.
- Hey, he's wearing
a stethoscope.
- Eddie, you really
quits with them,
I mean, Helen and Bayliss?
- Yeah, I'm quits.
- I'm glad, honey.
You know, she wasn't
for you anyway.
She ain't our kind.
- She's smart and pretty.
- No, she ain't.
- She's a mammal.
- Kind of sorry you ain't
gonna be a big singer though.
I was kind of looking forward
to getting all dolled up and--
- Eughhh!
- Again! Eugh!
- And having everybody
looking at us.
[♪♪♪]
- The morning papers
ought to be out.
- So what?
- So they ought to be full
about that fat slob
I knocked over last night.
- Mrs. [indistinct]
- That's so sick.
I bet you wish
they knew you did it
so you could get
your picture in the paper.
- Yeah, my name
and my picture in the paper.
Everybody look at me and say--
- Li'l Abner.
- There's Bob Moonie,
the big shot.
Why, I'd be a celebrity.
- I don't know why
I bother to talk to you.
You know something?
You're nuts.
- Oh, I'm just whimsical.
- Why do you want to be
a singer, Eddie?
Why?
- Would you just eat
your candy bar?
- 'Cause everybody
can look at you and say,
"That's Eddie Crane,
the big celebrity."
I'm the same way, Eddie.
'Cept I don't know
how to sing.
- Bitter.
- Oh, a tad.
- Does that make sense, man?
- Yeah. To you.
[Knocking on door]
- Halcygram.
- Put that thing away.
- Why, man?
We might have to
blast our way out of here.
- Nobody knows anything
about us.
Put it away.
- Iris, get the door
and find out who it is.
- We're shooting the dishes.
- What's going on in there?
- See, I told you the cops.
Let's blast 'em and make it--
- Shut up!
It's only the house dick.
Let me handle it.
- Oh, how accommodating .
- We're not jumping
on the beds.
- Yeah, what do you want?
- I have the manager with me.
- What the--?
Put it-- Geez !
- Open up!
- What should we do?
- Talk to him.
- Okay.
- Mystery guest,
enter and sign in please.
- Well, you see.
You see what they have done?
- What's this about the bill?
We ain't checked out yet?
And besides, Mr. Bayliss
is taking care of it.
- That's just it.
Mr. Bayliss called and said
that he won't be responsible
after this morning.
- That's it, see?
- We've decided
to stay 'til tonight.
We'll pay you
for the extra day.
- We don't want you.
- That's right.
You're undesirable tenants.
You'll have to get out.
Besides,
there's the matter
of the damage
you've done to the room.
You're gonna pay for that too.
- Pretty smooth, huh?
- Mister, why don't you
let us stay 'til tonight?
I promise we'll pay
for everything we broke.
- What did you do?
Bring protection with you
this time, chickie, huh?
- Don't get wise, son.
What's the matter with him?
- A bad cold.
Hey, fatso, you a real cop
or are you just
a chicken inspector?
- You don't like cops,
do you, sir?
- Don't stop doing that.
- No, I don't.
Not real cops
or play cops like you.
- Moon, shut up.
Go and take a walk
and get them cold pills for Ed,
like I asked you.
Go on.
Do you hear me?
- Ah, again!
- Oh, they got to hire
a continuity director.
- That boy's gonna
get in trouble some day.
- Yes, sir.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
Williams and Ree.
- Can we stay if Mr. Bayliss
tells you it's okay?
- Why, if Mr. Bayliss
says it's all right,
then that's good enough for us.
- All right,
let me make a phone call.
- Gee, if Mr. Bayliss says
I can kick you in the groin,
can I?
- Operator, get me
Majestic 2202, please.
I'm sorry about that mess.
We had a little--
Hello?
Oh.
- Oh.
- Helen?
- Hello.
- This is Eddie.
- Is Mr. Bayliss there?
- Oh.
- Can I talk to him please?
- Hello, Mr. Bayliss.
This is Eddie.
Sorry about the--
- Well, I think
you're throwing away
the chance of a lifetime, Eddie.
I had some big plans for you.
- Hello?
- I know, Mr. Bayliss,
that's what I wanted to
talk to you about.
Is it too late
to change my mind?
- You mean, you can do with
that recording date tonight?
- Yes, sir.
I realize, like you said,
this is my big chance
and I'd like
another crack at it.
- I know.
I haven't had a chance to call
and cancel the date yet
so everything'll be all right.
What's the matter, son?
Did you get scared?
- Yes, sir.
I got scared, that's it.
Look, Mr. Bayliss.
The hotel manager's here.
Will you tell him
it's okay for us to stay?
- Why, sure.
Oh, but listen, Eddie.
You get over to
Universe Recorders.
They're at Island Hollywood.
Now get there
as soon as possible
so you can start rehearsing
the recording gig tonight.
- Recording, yeah.
- And I'll meet you there.
- Yes, sir. I'll be there
in about an hour.
- Good.
Now put the manager on.
- It's my dad.
Says we can stay. Huh!
- Yes, Mr. Bayliss?
- Please charge everything
to me and, oh yeah,
give them anything they want.
- Oh, yes.
I understand.
- Mm-hm, in the groin. Right.
- Well, thank you very much.
Goodbye.
Well, I guess
everything's all right.
- Ha, ha, hewww!
- But would you please try to
keep your friends under control?
- I will.
- Thank you, sir.
- Well, I guess killing's okay
when it's sanctioned
by an agent.
- Yeah.
- Looks like you're gonna be
a big star after all, huh?
- Huh, yeah,
I decided to be a star.
- I got to get dressed.
I'm going over
to Universal Recorders.
- You want me to go with you?
- Heck, no, I--
I mean, oh...
- I'd like to get my stuff.
No. Is that it?
- That's it.
- Why don't you stay here
and straighten up?
- When in Hollywood,
visit Universal Recorders.
- Hi. You all right?
- Yeah.
- This your first record?
- It's my first anything.
I never even sung
before the TV show last night,
professionally, I mean.
- No kidding?
Well, you'll be all right.
You're moving mighty fast.
This is
the hottest label in town.
If your record clicks,
you'll be on top in no time.
- Click.
- I sure hope so.
- Do you, um,
d'you read music?
- 'Fraid not.
- No?
Well, that's all right.
None of the new artistes do.
That's what we have
this full dress rehearsal for
so you can get used to it.
Want to run through it
a couple of times?
- It would help.
- All right. If you'll--
- Put the dress on.
- Go ahead and use that mic,
why, we'll get going here.
Okay, boys, let's do the song
so Eddie can get the feel of it.
- I was like you last week.
I was the big star.
Now I do this.
- Charles Whitman!
[♪♪♪]
- Hi, Eddie.
- Cut, cut, cut, cut!
Get her out of there.
[Sighing]
- Let me explain about--
- Shhh, not now.
- Shnot now?
- It's all right.
You're here.
Would you like some coffee?
- Yeah.
- Cream?
- Black.
Where's Mr. Bayliss?
- He's over there.
I'll get your coffee.
- Psst. Hurry back.
- Uh, if you two
are done in there,
we'd like to cut a record.
- Eddie, you can take it easy
for a few minutes.
We've got to check
some levels here.
- It's snowing
back stage, Eddie.
- Glad you're back, Eddie.
- Thanks, Mr. Bayliss.
- That was terrific.
- I sure appreciate--
- Ah, forget all about that.
But I hope
you're not gonna
change your mind again,
though, are you?
- No.
- Eddie,
I want to talk to you.
- Have you see
this rash, Eddie?
- Now, Helen seemed to think
that you're in
some sort of trouble.
- Are you pregnant, Eddie?
- Now what is it, son?
Why don't you tell me?
- I can't.
- I can't understand
what you do
with a wild bunch of punks
like that.
And that's all they are,
you know?
- I know it.
- Then, why don't you
break away from them?
Tell 'em to leave you alone?
- I can't.
Don't you understand?
I can't.
- You mean, you don't want to?
- Of course I want to.
But I can't,
they won't let me.
- You know, I've known you
for well over an hour, Eddie,
and I think you're wonderful.
- That is I--
ah, forget it.
- They really have a hold
on you, haven't they?
♪ They really
Have a hold on you ♪
- Here's your coffee.
- Oh, thanks.
- It's scalding
my hand, hurry.
Ah, ah.
- Here's to us.
- To us?
- Staying in the spare room.
I forget to mention it.
It's okay, Eddie.
- Boy, and with cream!
Euk!
- Are you ready to try one?
- Yeah, I guess so.
- Excuse me, I've got to go
sing my number one hit single.
- We'll hear this
in the booth.
- I'll hear this
in my nightmares.
- I'll wait 'til it
comes out in the stores.
[♪♪♪]
- What's a mathematician
doing conducting?
[♪♪♪]
- It's beatnik music.
♪ ...thief with a thing
And the deal ♪
♪ A la la ♪
- ♪ You'd better be careful
Or you may be next ♪
♪ It strikes-- ♪
- Bang!
- ♪ When you never
Expect it to ♪
♪ Yes love is a thief ♪
♪ That will steal
The heart of you ♪
- ♪ And we're sorry
We popped that fat barkeep ♪
- ♪ Love wears a mask ♪
- ♪ A tight leather mask ♪
- ♪ Beware of that innocent
Look in its eyes ♪
♪ It hits-- ♪
- Bang!
- ♪ And there's nothing
That you can do ♪
- ♪ When you're backed up ♪
♪ By George you can't survive ♪
- ♪ Love is a thief that
You've got to surrender to ♪
[Sighing]
- He's really something special,
isn't he, Harry?
- Yeah.
- ♪ Laugh if you will-- ♪
- But I hope I didn't bite off
more than I can chew.
- You bit him too?
- What do you mean?
- You know, you were right.
That kid's in
a heap of trouble.
- What kind?
- Well, I don't know
but it's got something to do
with that gang
he runs around with.
- He's pals with
that Meyer Lansky character.
- Harry, we've got to help him.
- How?
- I don't know.
Talk to them,
explain to them, something.
Find out what it is, Harry.
- They could dress like
beatniks and go undercover.
- I don't know.
- Please? For me.
- Are they gonna kiss?
If they're gonna kiss,
I'll throw up, I promise.
- Hey, yuk.
Mushy stuff.
- She looks like
Donald Sutherland in drag.
- Crazy.
- ♪ Leather coat
Dom-ba-doom dom-da-dom-dom ♪
♪ Ducktail hair ♪
- Wait a minute,
wait a minute, kid.
Sing that again.
- What you mean--
♪ Leather coat
Dom-ba-doom da-da-da-- ♪
- Wait a minute,
wait a minute, wait a minute.
The other part.
- ♪ Ducktail hair ♪
- That's it, kid.
I'm gonna make you a star.
- Really? Wow!
- Yup.
- Gee, I don't know about this,
Colonel Robinson.
I'm just a simple
bass-ackwards country boy
who loves his mama.
What's so great about
being a star anyhoo?
[Clicking fingers]
Say, my own plasty-faced
butt-lady.
Huh, come here, baby,
I'll show you
the meaning of love.
5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
♪ Leather coat
Dom-ba-doom dom-da-dom-dom ♪
♪ Ducktail hair ♪
♪ Dom-ba-doom dom-da-dom ♪
I think that's a cut, Jimmy.
Let's go ahead.
Thank you, Topo Gigio.
Now for the newest singing
sensation, Tom Servo.
Thank you very much.
♪ Leather coat
Dom-ba-doom dom-da-dom-- ♪
I'm not finished.
- Okay.
- What's my motivation?
- Daddio, take 25.
- Okay.
- Want some?
- Um, uh.
- Oh, cut, cut, cut.
This Servo guy's useless.
This is the last time
we hire a leading man
with inoperable arms.
Stop Servo, you're fired.
Give me that Contino kid.
- But, but, but,
I didn't have a--
- Okay, cut.
♪ Leather bar
Slingshot briefs ♪
Say, I know you.
Don't you remember me?
Why are you leaving me
hanging like this?
I'm Tom Servo.
I'm Tom Servo!
- I never knew him.
- Ugh.
- Tom Servo, everything
he touched, he destroyed.
We'll be right back.
[♪♪♪]
- You're okay.
You went through a lot
today already.
- I think our story
is better than theirs.
- We're standing in his way,
is that it?
- Well, I don't know but I know
he's involved with you
in some sort of trouble,
isn't he?
- He snagged on me.
- He didn't tell me anything.
But look, I know
you're in some sort of a jam.
Now why don't you tell me?
Maybe I could help.
- [LAUGHING]
Why should you help us?
- Well, if everything goes
all right with Eddie,
we'll be together
a long time.
I'd just like to know
all about him and you and--
- Then why don't you ask Eddie?
- Well, he won't tell me
anything.
- That's our boy, Eddie.
He wouldn't squeal on us.
- Tonight on " Crossfire. "
- What did he tell you?
- Nothing, I said.
- "Nothing, I said."
You're lying
in your big fat teeth, Mister.
- Hey, Moon, take it easy.
- You think you can get
your boy off the hook
by turning us in,
isn't that it?
- Moon, shut up!
He don't know nothing.
- Yeah, that's it, isn't it?
- Hey, keep it down.
Some of us have to
rob a store in the morning.
- You've probably got
this place lousy with cops.
I was right.
- Duh, duh, duh, duh,
duh, duh, duh, duh--
- Down there.
Filthy with fuzz.
- You better get
out of here, quick.
- Uh-oh.
- Come on.
- I'm a pixie.
- You're goin' no place, Mister.
You invited yourself up here
and you are goin' to stay.
- Honestly, son, I don't know
what you're talking about.
- Let him go, Moonie.
He ain't gonna talk.
- No, he ain't gonna talk.
He ain't gonna
get a chance to talk.
Get back. Back!
- Moonie, stop it.
You're gonna get us all burned.
- What's the difference
if you kill 1, 2 or 100?
- Uh, 98.
- ...buddy Eddie too.
I've always wanted
to get Eddie.
- Johnny Longcrotch.
- You're the guy who's gonna
make Eddie a big celebrity,
ain't you?
Like me, a big celebrity.
D'you read the morning papers
this morning, Daddy, huh?
- Uh, just Taffy.
- I'm in the morning papers, me.
- Then read the super quiz,
man.
- ...that barkeep.
They don't know I done it.
Well, I'm gonna tell 'em
I done it.
- Well, I didn't recognize
your work.
- You don't know
what you are doing.
- I killed that fat barkeep!!
- Boy, isn't that interesting?
He took 10% out of the agent.
- You're crazy, Moonie!
You're crazy, crazy, crazy!
- What a nasty slice.
- What about our
continental breakfast?
- Hey, what's
going on in there?
[Knocking on door]
- Now we're in for it.
- Open up.
This is the house dick,
can you hear me?
- Uh-oh.
- What'll we do?
- I'll take care of 'em.
Come and get us, fuzz.
- Uh, technically,
would this now be considered
a killing spree?
- Mm-hm.
- No. No, no!
- Stop the over-acting.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Open up!
- Take that and this and that!
- Let's get out of here.
- Moonie,
I ain't goin' with you.
- Let's get out of here.
- I ain't goin' with you,
Moonie!
- Come with me!
- No!
- They shoot horse faces,
don't they?
- Hope so.
[Knocking on door]
- You lousy fucks.
Come and get us!
- He's going through puberty,
all of a sudden.
- This is the scene
that got him the part
in the big ballet premier.
[♪♪♪]
- East side, West side.
- Stop him!
He's got a drum set!
- Oh, he's fallen
into a board meeting.
- Manics!
- Oh, he hit Allan Sherman.
- You better stay here, sister,
you're not going anywhere.
- Not looking like that.
♪ Meet George Jetson!
Hah! ♪
[Laughing]
- That was a bad edit.
- Heh, the medium's
the message, jerk. Ha.
The printed word is dead.
- Okay, that's it, fellas.
'Til tonight.
- It ain't working.
- I'm sorry.
- Good going, Eddie.
Went very nice.
You won't forget
about 7 o'clock tonight?
- I'll be here.
- Okay, we'll see you then.
- My house, bring a casserole.
- Note to me, "Fire Eddie."
- Well, how do you feel?
- I'll make it.
Come here.
- That's far enough.
- I want to talk to you about
that phone call last night.
I didn't mean it.
- I know you didn't.
Neither did I.
About goodbye, I mean.
- Well, I didn't mean it first.
- About how I feel.
- I know.
I wish I could tell you
about myself but I--
- What are you afraid of?
- Escalators.
- That you won't love me.
- Honestly, darling, I love you
and nothing will change it.
- Don't say I didn't warn you.
[Phone ringing]
- Hello there.
- When's Mr. Bayliss
getting back?
He'll be here for the session,
won't he?
- Of course.
- Helen Tracy, telephone.
You can take it out there.
Brought to you by [indistinct].
- Hello?
Yes, this is she.
- ...dying...
- Hospital?
Well, what happened?
- Your [indistinct].
- Oh no.
- He just signed
the Hudson Brothers.
- Yes, of course,
I'll be right over.
Oh, poor Harry.
- What about Harry?
What happened?
- He's badly hurt.
- Hurt how? Accident?
- No. I sent him over
to your hotel to talk to--
- To talk to who?
Moonie and the others?
- There was a fight
or something.
Moonie stabbed him.
- Oh, no. That crazy--
- Mixed up, wonderful hoodlum.
- Eddie, please.
- I'll get him for this.
- I've got to get
to the hospital.
- I'm going with you.
There are some things
I've got to tell you on the way.
Things you ought to know,
come on.
- I have a hiatus hernia.
Thought you might
want to know.
- I got a really bad hip
going on.
- Twisted rotator cuff.
- Oh, right, a taxi in L.A.
This has got to be a movie.
- Oh, spare us not one moment
of their trip to the hospital.
- Well, I want to go
see my manager
but first I got to get
a rack of ribs.
- You kids go ahead.
Cab ride's on me.
- Okay, Myrtle, let's go back
and change the bedpans.
- Oh, you know,
that heart attack patient
is buzzing again.
- Danny Aiello!
- [GROANING]
Oh, but, son,
I'm gonna bury you.
Oh.
- Hey, let's put his hand
in warm water.
- Oh, Harry, I'm so sorry.
- Shot in the face, huh?
- Mr. Bayliss?
- You do have a big face.
- I want to tell you
how sorry I am.
That crazy--
- Hey, please forget it.
I'm okay.
- Relatives?
- No, I work for Mr. Bayliss.
- Oh.
- And my friends stabbed him.
- I'm Lieutenant Matten.
We got most of the gang
but the guy who cut up
Mr. Bayliss got away.
- Hey, you're Paul Frees.
- I hope so.
- The ones we have
in custody won't talk.
But the hotel manager gave us
a description of the other two.
- Two?
- There's Moonie
and Eddie Crane.
Mr. Bayliss,
you can talk now.
I wonder if you could
help us find 'em.
- Well, they did say something
about the La Brea Tar Pits.
- I couldn't tell you
where they are.
- Unless you wouldn't--
- Accessory after the fact
theater will return after this.
[♪♪♪]
- Meanwhile,
at the same time...
- What are you thinking about?
- You and me.
- And pegboard.
- But I know about it now
and it hasn't changed
the way I feel.
And you know how
Mr. Bayliss feels about you.
- I know.
The cops are looking for me.
You and Mr. Bayliss
lying to protect me.
I'm not gonna mess up
your life, Helen.
And I'm not gonna run
anymore.
- Eddie, please.
- It's no use.
- Mess up my life.
- You don't understand.
I've finally found
something to live for.
Everything I want
is right here.
- In dianetics.
- And I can't have it this way.
- Oh, Eddie.
- You understand
what I have to do.
- Yes.
- Pssssss.
Ow, my shoulder!
- Let's create the scene
from " Videodrome ."
- Tell 'em they can find
Eddie Crane here.
- Who?
- Oh, don't ask me to do that.
I can't.
- Please, for me?
- I'm no good on the phone.
- I'm gonna chicken out
the last minute.
If you love me,
do it for me.
Go on.
- Okay.
- Uh, is that a "Yes"?
- Okay, let's make it.
- The whole band
was listening?
- Hmm, National 29000.
[Phone ringing]
- You have reached a bald man.
Press 1 for--
- Got a man pickup.
Suspect Eddie Crane
at Universal Recorders.
- Okay.
[Police siren]
- Hey, quit whining.
♪ Left me fumbling
With the blues ♪
- Hey, what's this?
I found a wheat penny.
- Hmm, this is Juicy Fruit.
♪ Meet George Jetson
Hah! Uh! ♪
- [indistinct]
just drove by.
- Okay, that was fine,
Eddie, real fine.
- I didn't start yet.
- You want to hear
the playback?
- Can you hold it a minute?
I'll be right back.
- Yeah, sure, you bet.
- Gonna see if there's
any ham sandwiches left.
- Well, I've been bald
since I was 40.
- That's right.
Thank you.
- Oh great.
She's checking
her bank balance.
- Uh, can I use the phone?
- Did you do it?
Good.
- I am the gassed
meter reader.
[Hiccupping]
It's an old joke.
- Hey, Eddie.
- Oh, hi, Moon.
How was your spree?
- Thanks, all done, man.
- I'll be right back.
- I've got to help him
cinch his pants up.
- Well, whaddya know?
It says right here
that soup is good food.
- Hi, Eddie.
Surprised to see
your old buddy?
- Oh, is he here?
- Yeah, I thought
you'd be out of town by now.
Where you been?
You loaded?
- Oh, no, I'm not loaded.
I'm tired, man.
I've had a day.
- You know something, Moon,
they're looking for you.
- Yeah? You too, huh?
- I like that man.
- I'm sure glad
to see you, Moon.
- No kidding, Eddie?
I thought you'd be mad.
- Boy, that's [indistinct] .
- The way I leaned
on old Bayliss.
Boy, I really got him,
didn't I, Eddie?
I got him good.
- This is so intense.
- I done it for you, Eddie.
- For me, yeah?
- Yeah.
- You know something?
It's always for me, isn't it?
- When I went back
into that bar,
that fat barkeep Charlie
said he was--
- What are you talking about?
You're not talking
about the barkeep--
- Well, that's his name,
it's Fat W. Barkeep.
- I'm talking about Bayliss.
Bayliss.
Bayliss!
- Barkeep was his best work.
He's never topped himself.
- He said he was
gonna tell the cops
and they'd take you away
and burn you.
- You know something, Moon?
You're so sick,
you don't even know
when you're lying.
- Oh, Eddie,
what are you saying?
- Oh, he's too drunk
to even know...
- I done it for you, man,
so you could be a big shot.
Did you read
the evening papers, Eddie?
- Come on, here, man.
Read 'em about that, man.
- You're a punk.
- I'm not a punk.
I'm a new romantic, all right?
- After I come all this way
so we could go off together
like we always did.
[Laughing]
Here, remember that store
Eddie knows to hold up?
Well, I was thinking,
we could go down there
and grab us some quick loot
and get down to Mexico
and be bandidos.
- Yeah, and then
we can ride Yoshi
to the Mushroom Kingdom.
- How does that move ya,
Eddie, man?
- We're going somewhere
together.
But it ain't gonna be Mexico.
- Goin' up the river.
The Big House, the Pen,
the Hoosegow,
the Clink, the Lock-up.
- You're gonna turn me in, man?
- I'll turn you in--
to a decent human being.
- Now I'm awful glad
you said that, Eddie.
'Cause now I can tell you
why I really came.
I was gonna wait 'til
I get down to Mexico
but now's a good time
as any, man.
- Grammar, Moon. Grammar!
- I'm gonna get you.
Man, I'm gonna get you good.
Now, I'm gonna spread you
all over this alley.
- There it is!
- You know, that is how
I imagined Dean Moriarty.
- Come on, punk.
Get me, I'm here.
[♪♪♪]
- Bernacko, no.
- Swing and a miss.
[indistinct] now.
- Let me tell you, that--
- This one's for [indistinct] .
- Gonna tammy towel you, man.
- Well, Berretta or Tumor
should be here any minute.
- Man, for a recording studio,
they got a ton of garbage.
- ♪ Meet George Jetson ♪
♪ Jane his skirt ♪
- You know, they're gonna get
really messy playing that way.
- Oh, they got
their playing clothes on.
- Oh, good.
- Easy-opening hand.
- You know, if any real
beatniks come by,
it's really gonna be
embarrassing.
- Mm-hm.
- Eddie? Eddie!
- Eddie, break-time's over.
We're ready for you.
- Eddie! Look out!
- Another break in continuity!
- I hate you,
garbage can, I hate you.
- Wait a minute,
do that in the 5-8.
I think you've got
something there.
[Police siren]
- Uh, Eddie, we really need you
to finish your hit record.
- Uh, your little friend will
still be in the garbage can
when we're done.
- That's good for the quads,
you know?
- That's right.
[Police siren]
- Uh, you guys seen
any hoodlums around here?
- All right, show's over.
Nothing to see here.
Go home, people.
- I'm Eddie Crane.
- Let's go.
- Hey, give me a second,
will you?
- Uh, 1001...
- Hey, I'd like a little
of that action too,
if you don't mind.
Then we got to go.
- Come on.
Plenty of time for that
in the Big House.
- All right, Eddie,
scooch over,
I'm riding shotgun.
- You two play nice
or I'll turn this thing around.
- Let that be a lesson to you.
- Morrisey was in this.
- No wonder
it was so depressing.
- Yeah. I wonder what's
gonna happen to him.
- Oh, 5 to 10.
- No, he'll hire
a high-powered beatnik lawyer.
[Laughing]
- You know, Joel,
I have to say
this was the best
Tony Travis film I've ever seen.
- Well, for once,
I'm gonna have to agree
with you, little buddy.
Have you seen Crow around?
- Yeah, I saw him running
after Gypsy with a knife.
- Oh, okay, well,
this is a letter.
I think it's time to read it.
It's from a woman named Cee
in Pearl City, Hawaii.
Let's put that on
still [indistinct].
Okay, and that.
And Cee writes,
"Dear Joel and the Bots.
"Forced into the bleak
isolation of my room
"by an angry mother,
my punishment is to write,
"'I will not call my mom
a dickweed' a million times.
"Before I begin this
seemingly impossible task,
"I must know in the interest
of justice for all,
is 'dickweed' a swear word?"
Um, no.
- Yes.
- No.
- No, it's definitely
not a swear word.
- No, it's clean.
You're cool.
You can stop writing,
"I will not call my mom
a dickweed."
- No, no!
- Agh, agh.
Agh, Croow.
- Where'd she go, man?
Where'd she go?
- Croow,
put that rubber knife away,
you're scaring Gypsy.
- I did it for you, Eddie.
- Oh, great,
he's in Moon mode again.
- That's right.
And now I'm gonna
moon you, man.
I'm gonna moon you.
- Well, that's gonna be tough
'cause you really don't
have a hinder to speak of.
- That's it.
That's it!
- Aghh!
- Oh, oh.
- Take care of my turtle.
- I will, Tommy.
- Stop my milk delivery.
- Okay, I will--
I will do it.
- Pick up my mail.
Cancel subscription
to "National Review."
- Okay.
- Continue to tape
"Baywatch" for me.
- All right.
- Take my step aerobics class
every Tuesday.
- All right.
Come on.
Okay, come on, get up.
Here, come on, you two.
Come on, face forward.
Say the words, come on.
BOTH:
Okay.
- Whaddya think, sirs?
- [WHISPERS]
Dickweed.
- Well, Joel, there's
a lot of heat around us now.
Several toy companies
are interested
in making dolls
in our likeness
and we're taking
a lot of meetings today.
- Who's going to drive,
your plumpiness?
- Push the button, Frank.
Push the button.
I'll do it.
- Agghhh.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Just a sec.
[♪♪♪]